[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
TWO MONTHS EARLIER
[people chattering]
[♪ jazz music playing]
[Geonyoung] They say that in this world,
no one stays your friend
or your enemy forever.
Which means that anyone
can stab you in the back at any moment
for their own personal gain.
There's no telling
when you might be betrayed.
But here's the saying
that rings truer to me right now.
"The enemy of your enemy is your friend."
[patrons chattering]
-[soldier] Sir!
-Sit down, sit down, it's okay.
At ease, guys. At ease. Sit down.
[Geonyoung] Colonel Ahn.
[Jaeho] Sorry I'm late.
It's fine. Haven't been here long.
Can you believe it's so hot
at this time of night?
[Geonyoung] Tell me about it.
-I appreciate you showing up, Colonel.
-[chuckles]
If you call me, Geonyoung,
then I come running.
-Excuse me?
-Yeah?
Two bowls of gukbap
and one order of suyuk please.
[cook] You got it.
-You're drinking, right?
-Yeah, sure.
-Here.
-Oh, uh…
It's hot out,
I'm gonna get a beer instead.
All right.
[clears throat]
-[Jaeho] Can I grab a beer?
-[cook] Sure.
[Jaeho] Here, you want some?
I always tried to see you
at the prosecutor's office,
but you avoided me.
Yeah, that's why I wound up
an unemployed loser,
and you turned into a bigwig
of national security.
Oh, come on now.
You know, ever since high school,
I've just been trying to catch up to you,
and I'm still way behind.
[Geonyoung chuckling]
Ah, that's nice.
When I heard about you,
I was wondering how you were doing
and what you might be up to.
-[chuckles]
-You should've reached out sooner.
You think I wouldn't be able
to help you out?
So what have you been doing all this time?
I mean, what options did I really have?
[chuckles] You know
those Gangnam apartments?
-I worked on all those.
-You worked construction?
[chuckles] Not a lot of options
for an ex-con.
Sometimes you take crappy jobs
to put food on the table.
[chuckling]
-Well, thanks. [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
[sighs]
Ah, that's good.
Mmm. [sniffles]
[Jaeho] Oh.
Your hand…
Yeah, I hurt it a little.
I, uh, can't straighten it anymore.
-[laughs]
-Oh, wow.
Guess I'm an invalid now.
[sighs]
What's in the bag?
Well, I had to have
something to show after all these years.
Take a look.
[clears throat]
PERSONAL RECORD: BAEK KITAE
PERSONAL RECORD: CHEON SEOKJUNG
Chief Cheon Seokjung.
His slush fund records.
It's 70 billion won.
[♪ tense music playing]
Seventy billion?
BAEKHO TRADING CEO BAEK SOYEONG
You and your agency can't
just serve as lackeys
for the KCIA forever, right?
You should take advantage
of your opportunities.
Oh, we're their lackeys? [chuckles]
When did you
have time to do all of this?
It wasn't that long.
Just took seven years. [chuckles]
[dog barking in distance]
[♪ music continues]
[blows nose, sniffles]
[sighs]
[fire crackling]
Now,
I want you to swear you'll do one thing.
Tell me what it is.
Once you take down Cheon Seokjung
and Baek Kitae, promise me
you'll help me get my old job back.
I can't live as an ex-con
for the rest of my life.
Can I?
I'm shocked
by how much you've changed. [chuckles]
-[glasses clink]
-[chuckles]
[♪ theme music playing]
SPECIAL ADVISOR JANG GEONYOUNG
[lighter flicks open]
[exhales]
[lighter strikes]
Ah, I'm glad you're here, Colonel Baek.
-[Jaeho] Good afternoon, sir.
-[door closes]
-You been waiting long?
-[Jaeho] He just got here.
[Geonyoung] Well, take a seat.
[♪ tense music playing]
Baek, go ahead.
Take a seat.
[Geonyoung sighs]
All right, let's see,
do I have everything?
[papers rustling]
Oh, thanks.
Two soldiers… [grunts] …ought
to share a few smokes, am I right?
Huh?
Here. Oh.
-Mmm.
-What are you doing? Don't be rude.
Well, Colonel Baek,
I'm excited to work with you.
Starting tomorrow,
you'll be reporting here.
Help him. Give him the support he needs.
We should go grab lunch together.
After all, we're a team now.
[Jaeho] Sounds good.
[phone ringing]
Mmm. Excuse me.
This is Jang Geonyoung.
[♪ music continues]
[Geonyoung exhales deeply]
IKEDA YUJI …70 BILLION THROUGH
BAEKHO TRADING FROM 1974 TO 1979
[sighs]
Baek, I'm sorry,
but we'll have to have lunch
some other day.
I've got to head out.
[whispers] Make sure
he doesn't call anyone.
Well, Colonel, we'll see you tomorrow.
Uh, by all means,
take your time and finish your cigarette.
-[Jaeho] All right. See you later, sir.
-Mm-hmm.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Open fire!
[knocks]
[Geonyoung] Mr. Baek Kitae.
Long time no see.
What the…
I'm a special advisor to the JIH.
Ikeda Yuji.
Or should I say, Choi Yuji.
You two haven't changed at all.
What the hell are you up to? What is this?
What's it look like? I'm doing my job.
-Get her out of the car.
-[door opens]
[Kitae] Get your hands off her. Hey!
What do you think you're doing? [spits]
You assholes don't know who I am, huh?
We're on orders from General Hwang.
He received a tip
concerning national security.
Please cooperate, Director Baek.
What tip, soldier?
That a member of the Yakuza
is smuggling 70 billion won in cash
into the country.
And now the acting KCIA director just
happens to be riding in a car with her.
So then…
how about me and you
have a chat later in private?
Listen to me.
You're going to go wait quietly
at the KCIA.
Unless you want bigger problems with me.
What…
you gonna shoot the director?
Let's go.
There's no reason to pick a fight.
-We'll talk at the station.
-Take her away!
Get the money.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Kitae muttering] Son of a bitch.
Damn it!
[huffs]
[Haksu] They took Choi Yuji to the
Joint Investigation Headquarters, and--
What about the money?
They took all of it.
DEPUTY DIRECTOR PYO HAKSU
What a shit show.
Those fucking bastards.
At least it's not me.
[Geonyoung] They can talk all they want
about constitutional reform
and direct presidential elections,
but in the end, the only thing
that changes the world is money.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Bitches!
[Geonyoung] Politics is no different
than business.
[screams]
[Geonyoung] Trust, confidence,
loyalty, even people…
at the end of the day, all of these things
can be bought with money.
[panting]
[Geonyoung] The money
I intercepted from Baek Kitae
was supposed to secure the presidency
for Cheon Seokjung.
But now, I'm going to take it
and use it as a weapon.
It's finally time
to go for my enemies' throats.
[chuckles]
Wow.
Seventy billion.
Baek lined his pockets, huh?
If it weren't for you,
it looks like he would've
sucked the whole country dry eventually.
[Geonyoung chuckles]
I wonder what exactly
his plan was here, you know?
Cheon Seokjung had
to have some larger end goal.
I mean, how would you even spend this?
Baek Kitae wants to swallow
this country whole.
-In one go.
-[scoffs]
That sneaky, thieving little bastard.
We have targets now.
Baekho Trading is first.
And then Cheon Seokjung's slush fund
will be tied to Baek's meth operation.
Which means that we can
destroy them for good.
Uh…
that's going to be… pretty difficult.
We haven't had a memorial service
for the president yet.
Hang on.
What does that have to do
with taking down Baek?
Bringing him down is fine,
but it's the meth…
-It's gonna look bad.
-[scoffs]
Uh, I'm confused.
What do you mean by that?
We're after him because he's dealing meth.
[laughing]
Ah, somehow you're still not getting it.
Jang, look. Think about this for a second.
If it gets out that the men closest
to the president were pushing drugs,
how do you think
the public's going to respond?
Essentially, it would end up
with the president's name
being dragged through the mud.
We have to preserve the legacy
of this country's leadership, don't we?
He's a drug pusher
and he'll pay the price. Simple as that.
General Hwang.
We have an opportunity
to make it clear to the public
how we deal with criminals.
This is how we root them out
and get rid of drug pushers for good.
This is how we preserve
our country's legacy and protect--
All right,
I understand what you're saying.
Let's just circle back to this after
the president's official memorial service.
For now, leave the meth out of it
and bring him down with the money.
Look, we have plenty of it
right in front of us, don't we?
That'll keep things…
-[sighs]
-…nice and squeaky clean.
[Haksu] You all right?
What happened to Choi? Did you find out?
[Haksu] Mmm, well…
they took her to the JIH
to interrogate her.
Can you believe that?
Jang Geonyoung teamed up with those guys.
Never thought I'd live to see that.
And the money?
I assume
they'll be holding onto it for a while.
All done.
[Kitae sighs]
The good news is…
they still don't have
any hard evidence yet.
They can't do much
with that kind of money right away.
As long as Choi doesn't start blabbing.
[lighter thuds]
How do you think
Jang Geonyoung knew where to go?
There's gotta be a leak.
From Japan, or someone who works with us.
[sighs]
So, do you think Choi can hold out?
-They'll probably put her through hell.
-[knock on door]
[door opens]
[sighs] Get out.
Hey.
I expect you to greet me, asshole.
Just say…
Piece of shit.
[door closes]
I did a thorough sweep, sir.
There were no bugs.
There's nothing to be concerned about.
Put a few guys on Pyo Haksu.
I want a report on everything,
everyone he meets.
Of course, sir. I'm on it.
Takahashi Kazuo.
He's stuck by Choi Yuji's side
for ten years.
My guess is, he's been holding onto
the ledger for a while.
PERSONAL RECORD
Knowing Yuji,
there's no way she'd keep the money
and the ledger in the same place.
If that ledger gets found
by anybody in the JIH,
we'll be dead. So go find him now.
Copy that.
[door opens]
-[phone ringing]
-[faint chattering]
-A yakuza from Osaka named Choi Yuji.
-Yeah?
[Kihyun] Section Chief Park.
Yeah? I got it.
How have you been, sir?
Oh. Baek, what are you doing here?
I received an assignment here
that begins this morning.
-I'm looking forward to--
-[chuckling] Oh, no.
Come on, you didn't have to do this.
All right, thanks.
You have any questions, let me know.
Thanks, sir. Much appreciated.
Oh, Baek.
Yes, sir?
Did you hear about it?
Hear about what?
Ikeda Yuji, we caught her.
Word is she's a member of the Yakuza.
Why was she brought in?
She brought money into Busan illegally.
And lots of it.
[sighs] How much?
Seventy billion.
Just imagine how many cartons
70 billion would buy you.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[sighs] Anyway, thanks for these.
-Sure.
-[blows]
[typewriter keys clacking]
[investigator] Oh, good morning, ma'am.
Miss Oh, a Yakuza woman named Choi Yuji
got busted for smuggling 70 billion won.
Seventy billion?
Yeah, it's making waves in the department.
[door closes]
Choi Yuji. You brought her in here?
Yes.
-[sighs]
-Hey, you
could've told me about this beforehand.
Why exactly would I do that?
What good would that do?
Well, never mind.
The raw materials for their meth
came in from Taiwan.
So I'm gonna get a warrant
for Baek Soyeong, now that we have proof.
[sighs]
You wanna give it a shot?
Take a crack at Choi Yuji?
Really?
Mmm.
[Yejin] Miss Choi Yuji.
Why did you smuggle
70 billion won into Korea?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Did Baek Kitae put you up to it?
[screaming in distance]
All of that money
came from selling meth, isn't that right?
And then you went and laundered it
into Chief Cheon's slush fund.
[door opens]
[Yejin on speakers] Hey, Miss Choi.
What, can't you talk?
You're just gonna keep your mouth shut?
[chuckles]
[Yejin] You clearly don't understand
the situation you're in.
Yeah, you probably think
the whole world just turns for you
with a face like that.
[scoffs] You got another thing coming.
[chuckles]
Yeah, and how would you know?
Moron.
-[Yejin] What?
-[slurping loudly]
[Yejin] "Moron?" Hey.
Listen to me carefully.
Right now, Korea's under martial law.
So the military controls
the whole country.
Got it?
You know what that means
for your situation?
What's your point?
You think I care?
You know I'm Japanese, right?
[exclaims]
That makes no fucking difference!
Doesn't mean a damn thing!
Are you listening?
I said Korea is under martial law.
Which means
everything is different right now.
And nobody in this country
is playing by the rules anymore.
It doesn't matter where you're from,
'cause you're not in Japan!
You're in Korea!
If you're not careful,
a little yakuza girl like you
could wind up dead in no time.
-[snickering]
-Is that funny?
Yeah. All right, I get it.
-Just give me a smoke, okay?
-What?
You little bitch.
[humming]
[faint screaming]
[doors bang]
[sighs]
[faint screaming continues]
I bet you think you and Baek Kitae
are gonna last forever.
You've shared a bed… [exhales sharply]
…you've shared your money…
You two have shared everything. Right?
I mean, a pair of drug pushers
in love with each other?
That's pretty crazy. Right?
Not very romantic, is it?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Hey, am I wrong about you two?
So the ledger
for Cheon's 70 billion won fund.
If you can get it for me,
you'll walk out of here alive.
Hmm?
I have Japanese papers, sir.
Contact the embassy, they'll sort it out.
The prosecutor told you
nobody cares about that.
Were you not listening?
Don't give me that crap.
The country's under martial law.
You know you're screwed.
Tell me where I can find it. The ledger.
I have Japanese papers, sir.
Please contact the embassy.
[Geonyoung scoffs]
Listen, smart-ass.
[faint screaming continues]
Do you hear that?
[screaming intensifies]
Really, can you hear that? Are you deaf?
[high-pitched screaming]
You're a criminal.
Okay, tough guy.
Now you listen to me.
You have two choices.
You either die and vanish in here,
or you walk out alive.
Where's the slush fund ledger?
[♪ music continues]
[scoffs]
[bucket rattles]
[Geonyoung] Get in here!
Tie her up.
You staying, Prosecutor Oh?
You can leave if you don't wanna watch.
[sighs]
Choi Yuji.
The ledger for Cheon's slush fund,
tell me where it is.
Right now.
[faint screaming]
Kitae, I have a feeling
the KCIA is crawling with rats.
Isn't it?
How the hell did they know where to go?
Sir, it's my fault.
[Seokjung] Now what?
We're just gonna let someone else
walk away with all of it?
Without the money, that shit heel
Hwang Daesik is gonna string us up
from the nearest tree as soon as he can.
I'll put everything back in order.
Just give me more time.
Are fucking kidding me?
[sighs]
I hear your brother joined
the Joint Investigation Headquarters.
[sighs]
What, you…
you weren't aware?
[scoffs]
You don't talk
to your own brother anymore?
[sighs]
Can you really…
trust him after this?
My brother is not going to be a problem.
When it comes down to it,
and you're fighting for money and power…
[scoffs]
…sharing blood is meaningless.
BAEKHO TRADING
ORGANIZATION CHART
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-[chattering]
-[phone ringing]
[typewriter keys clacking]
-Chief.
-What is it?
[investigator] This guy here,
he's a junior from my neighborhood.
So what was Hwang's response?
[sighs]
He can't be persuaded.
He's the most stubborn bastard
I've ever met.
-[sighs]
-And we haven't
even had a service for the president yet.
-Slow down. Let's pull back a little.
-[scoffs]
Look, sir.
[sighs] We're military men. Soldiers.
Our job is to obey orders.
You've been around the block.
You should know that by now.
Well,
I should probably get back to work.
[♪ music continues]
[Kang] Uh-huh, I'm on it. Yes.
I'll make sure I look into it. All right.
[investigator] You can't
write the story like that.
Hey, Miss Oh, um,
you wanna grab a drink? I wanted to--
70 BILLION THROUGH BAEKHO
TRADING FROM 1974 TO 1979
[knocks on door]
[clears throat]
Come in.
Excuse me, sir, do you have a minute?
What is it?
[sighs]
You settling in, Baek? Feel at home?
Yes, sir. It's been fine.
Baek Soyeong.
I'll get a warrant to bring her in.
[inhales deeply] Hold off for now.
Why?
Hold off.
Why should I?
Are you being difficult right now?
Can you just try to explain your approach?
Why am I supposed to stand down?
Because you take orders from me!
You are not…
[inhales sharply]
You are not doing anything
without my approval.
But why?
Don't tell me the higher-ups
are stopping you again.
[Geonyoung sighs]
Just focus on the slush fund for now.
Our first priority is finding the ledger,
then we go for Cheon,
and finally, Baek Kitae.
[sighs]
[lighter flicks open]
All right, let me ask you something.
Are you sure going this far is…
responsible?
[lighter closes]
[thuds]
Say more.
Look, going after Baek is one thing.
Torturing prisoners is something else.
I know times have changed and everything.
But everyone deserves dignity.
People deserve basic human rights.
[shouting] You saying I should feel guilty
for the way I handle a bunch of animals?
Is that it?
You want to go back to the old days?
Tell me what you want from me.
How is it that becoming a prosecutor
didn't change you one bit?
The country is being turned upside down.
Yeah, what about you?
Because you've obviously changed.
Get out.
Go on.
[♪ somber music playing]
[door slams]
[sighs]
BAEKHO TRADING INC.
[Kang huffs] What the hell? Shit.
I guess they're closed.
Hey, where'd you say she lived?
Remember,
we're getting meat delivered today,
so marinate some bulgogi.
And either throw the abalone out
or take it home. It's not fresh.
Oh, and get the snacks ready
for Minju on time for once.
Yes, ma'am.
Wow.
Is that hanbok new?
It's been a long time, Miss Baek.
How's your daughter been?
PROSECUTOR OH YEJIN
[scoffs]
A prosecutor?
Well, look who's moving up.
I know, right?
I even get to eat pineapple now.
Mmm. That's tasty.
Why'd you come to my house today?
[Yejin] Mmm.
Well, the factory was closed, so,
I stopped by your home,
hoping you'd be around
'cause I missed you.
You know the meth operation at…
Baekho Trading?
[Soyeong scoffs]
What are you talking about? [sighs]
You drunk right now?
Why did you close up shop there?
I bet your brother told you to.
Slow down.
You do know who my brother is, right?
-Director of the KCIA.
-Whoa.
You really think
you can threaten me, bitch?
You're a two-bit prosecutor.
[laughing]
[fork clatters]
[Soyeong breathing heavily]
You're turning into a junkie trying
to clean up after your brother, huh?
-Let go!
-Baek Soyeong, listen.
You know your brother's department
is weak now.
So get your head on straight
before you wind up in a world of hurt.
You know Choi Yuji, right?
She's locked up at the Joint Investigation
Headquarters right now. [scoffs]
You wanna stay out of prison
with your brother, right?
Then I'd talk if I were you.
Screw you.
Aren't you still a mother?
For your daughter's sake,
get off the junk already.
[sighs] Ugh, geez.
[Soyeong breathing heavily]
-[door opens]
-I hate that little shit.
-[door closes]
-Hey, come here!
Throw some salt outside!
[whispers] Damn it.
[breathes heavily] Oh.
[chuckles awkwardly]
Minju, there you are.
Let's have a snack. Come here.
Hurry, let's go.
[breathes deeply]
[Yejin] I was right.
-Soyeong's an addict.
-Shit.
Start tracking down the other members.
Yeah, but Jang told us
our priority should be the slush fund.
You sure this is okay?
Look, Baek's my target
for drug trafficking.
He's the reason I wound up in Seoul.
Right, let's go.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Have you two met before today?
Yes, we met one time, briefly.
When the president was still alive.
By the way, Director Baek,
I can sense you're blessed
with remarkably good energy.
Thank you, ma'am.
You two only met once
and she still recognizes you.
I assume he…
he must've made quite an impression.
Well, I suppose, I just
look at someone and say what I'm seeing.
Madam Shin worked
for the president. [sighs]
When he was in office,
she helped with a lot of major decisions.
She and I are quite close as well.
Oh. I see.
Okay, so,
the woman that's in prison,
you mentioned she's Japanese?
[Kitae] Yes.
She's originally Zainichi Korean,
but she managed
to get citizenship in Japan.
Well, then, I should speak
to the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
If you end up getting involved personally,
it'll be a bad look for everyone.
Well, since I've been having problems
thanks to the pricks
over at the JIH lately.
[Kitae sighs]
I'm sure Director Baek can
handle the ledger on his own.
Would you work with me for a while
to help resolve some of these issues?
What, for free?
[scoffs]
Come on, I'm not Hwang.
I don't expect any free favors.
You'll be well compensated
if things go off without a hitch.
[laughing]
Don't worry, it was just a joke.
You seem a little on edge today.
Truth is, it really wouldn't
make a difference anyway.
It's all in the name
of our country, isn't it?
[chuckles]
In any case,
I'll pray nice and hard for both of you
from today onward, all right?
[chuckles]
All right, turn your head a little.
Mmm, a little further to the right.
[shutter clicks]
[in Japanese] Thanks.
[phone rings]
[in English] This is Baek Kihyun.
[Kitae] You joined the JIH?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Yes.
[sighs]
How come you didn't say anything?
I was going to.
Jang Geonyoung's working there
as a special consultant, huh?
Yes.
Ahn put in a good word for him, I guess.
They're from the same town,
went to the same high school.
These small town connections. Damn it.
[sighs] Don't get comfortable over there.
Jang Geonyoung specifically chose you
because he wants to mess with your head.
You understand?
Yeah. I'm aware.
[Jaeho] About Colonel Baek…
Shouldn't we get ahead of this?
How long you plan to let him be?
I could talk to him.
Just leave him alone.
All these eyes on him, it won't be long.
He'll figure it out. He's not a child.
You think Baek would
betray his own brother?
Let's wait a bit longer
and see what he chooses.
He either goes down with his brother,
or he survives with us.
How's Choi Yuji holding up?
Pretty good for now, I guess,
but it'll get worse.
Believe me, she's solid.
All you have to do
is keep an eye on Jang
and report to me afterward.
Yeah. I'm on it.
What about Soyeong?
Is she gonna be okay or what?
Don't worry about that.
She's not their target anyway.
Yes, sir. Copy that.
[Geonyoung] Colonel Baek,
you heading home yet?
I've got a few things to do.
I'm just gonna finish up first.
But it's getting late.
How about you finish in the morning?
Soju sound good?
I'm buying the first round.
Sounds great.
How about some dwaeji gukbap
and some makgeolli?
You should head home, Colonel Ahn.
Your family's waiting. [chuckles]
I think
it's just gonna be us.
-Okay, sure.
-All right.
-I'll be waiting outside.
-Great.
[grunts]
The memories are all rushing back to me,
sitting here with you.
One night I was at this same table,
but I was with your brother.
We had a bottle of soju, just like this.
And we were here, eating dwaeji gukbap,
on a rainy night like tonight.
What is it you want from me?
Not much, to be honest.
Well, actually, there is one thing.
It's not a big deal.
Sorry, would you, um,
mind if I speak candidly
with you from now on?
After all, we're a team now.
We are a team, aren't we?
Oh, of course. Be candid.
[chuckling] I knew it.
You're just like your brother.
The boss man.
You're just as much
of a big shot as he is.
Here you go. Let me pour you a drink.
Look, stop beating around the bush.
Why'd you bring me into the JIH?
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Use your head and look alive.
Okay, what exactly does that mean?
You're better off taking it at face value.
Just do your best to see things
as they are.
You're in a different world now.
You can't keep living
like you always have.
[scoffs]
So I'm supposed to…
to betray my own brother?
[glass thuds]
Minju.
Who's gonna raise her?
Are you willing to do that
if Baek Soyeong goes to jail?
[scoffs]
[♪ tense music playing]
[grunts]
The truth is, uh…
that your family complicates things
all the time, right?
If you want your sister to live
and your niece to have a normal childhood,
you have to ensure you survive first.
What do you want?
What do I have to do?
Make sure you keep an eye
on Baek Kitae's activities.
Watch him and find out what he's planning.
You think your brother's gonna sit still?
He's going to try something.
[drink pouring]
You're in hell right now, aren't you?
You want to escape that
and get your life back?
Choice is yours.
Pick a side.
All right, then, how about we go elsewhere
and get another round?
This weather makes me thirsty.
Mmm.
Colonel Baek.
See you tomorrow.
[grunts]
[sighs]
♪ …toy train goes chugging along ♪
♪ Carrying cookies and candy ♪
[sighs] Kitae, what on earth is going on?
-The lab. Did you shut it down?
-Mm-hmm.
I moved everything out after you called.
All right, tell the others
to keep their mouths shut
and stay away from there for a while.
Wait, but don't tell me we're gonna
stop production for good. Are we?
No, we won't be shutting down.
Why would we?
We'll ramp back up
once things settle down.
How long?
Just wait.
First, I have to take back
what they stole.
But what did they steal?
♪ To our baby in Mom's room ♪
Have a good day, Uncle Kitae.
[Kitae] All right.
[Soyeong sighs, grunts]
♪ The little toy train
Goes chugging along-- ♪
Go play somewhere else!
[sighs] Shit.
[breathing heavily]
-[door opens]
-[footsteps approach]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Sir, I've got some news.
What is it?
A notice from
the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
NOTICE REGARDING
DETAINED ZAINICHI KOREAN
[Jaeho] The Japanese government
has lodged a formal complaint.
We also heard from
the Martial Law Command.
They both want Ikeda Yuji released,
effective immediately.
[phone rings]
-Yeah?
-Mr. Jang, this is the guard post.
Your sister is here to see you, sir.
Put her on.
Excuse me. Where's
the Joint Investigation Headquarters?
Oh, the JIH? It's right over there.
-Oh, thank you.
-Sure.
[phone ringing in distance]
-How can I help you?
-Uh…
[Geonyoung] Hyeeun.
Oh, good morning.
Come on in.
I should introduce you to Colonel Baek.
He and I have been working together.
Say hello.
Right. Hello. Jang Hyeeun, sir.
She's my sister.
Baek Kihyun, Miss Jang.
Let's go.
I've heard so much
about this department lately.
The JIH has been all over the news.
So how have you been doing?
You know, same as usual.
What about you? Are you doing okay?
[chuckles softly]
Yeah, everything's fine.
Why do you ask?
You're thin and pale, Geonyoung.
I'm getting worried about you.
I've been busy, that's all.
Don't worry, I'm okay.
[inhales deeply] Hyeeun.
I'm not the same man I used to be.
You don't
need to worry about me, all right?
But I still do. I can't help it.
[sobbing]
[Geonyoung sighs]
-[phone ringing]
-[sniffling, sobbing]
Hey, let me call you right back.
[Hyeeun crying]
Sorry. I'm being silly.
I almost forgot.
Here are some leftovers
from Dad's funeral yesterday.
You should eat some of it.
I wish I'd been with you.
I'm really sorry.
It must've been hard on your own.
Uh, not at all actually.
-[phone ringing]
-[Hyeeun chuckles]
Yes?
Yeah, I'll be there soon.
[radio host] …will mostly be clear.
-[grunts]
-[gasping]
[radio host] …slightly lower
than yesterday, so it'll feel chilly.
In Seoul, we're looking at a low
of 3 degrees Celsius…
-[radio turns off]
-[Yuji gasps]
[Geonyoung] Bring her here.
[Yuji gasping]
[grunting]
[coughs]
[wheezing, panting]
[investigator] Got her? [grunts]
[Yuji breathing raggedly]
Everyone out.
[Yuji shivering]
[Geonyoung] Choi Yuji.
-[shivering]
-Choi Yuji!
-[door closes]
-[continues shivering]
We were contacted by the Japanese
Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
It says right here…
they want you released immediately.
[Yuji breathing heavily]
[♪ tense music playing]
[Geonyoung sighs]
You think I'm gonna
let you walk out of here
because of some official document? Huh?
[breathing shakily]
-Tell me where the ledger is.
-[breathing heavily]
Tell me where it is! Where is it? Come on!
Answer me or you're dead.
Where's the ledger?
Say it! Where is it?
[Kihun] Director Baek,
I found Takahashi Kazuo.
Where is he?
Busan Hotel. Room 308.
Listen, stay until I get there.
-I'm on the way now.
-Yes, sir.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-[Kitae] Where's the ledger?
-[♪ music continues]
What happened to the kumicho?
We'll get her out soon, trust me on that.
Until then, I'm gonna need you
to hand over the slush fund ledger.
The kumicho said
that I shouldn't give it to anyone.
I already talked to Choi Yuji.
I won't be able to get her out
unless you hand it over.
You know what happens
if that ledger gets picked up by the JIH?
All of us are going down.
[♪ music continues]
[brakes screech]
[Kazuo] Hang on.
You mean you and the kumicho
had a conversation recently?
The JIH took her into custody,
put her in some prison to torture her.
How could you have talked to her?
Oh, you know,
you really ask too many questions.
[grunting]
[groans]
[grunts]
[breath trembling]
Bastard.
[panting]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
-Move!
-[housekeeper exclaims]
[screams]
[Kitae breathing heavily] Oh, shit.
-[gunshots]
-[housekeeper yelps]
[Kitae breathing heavily]
[♪ music continues]
[breathing heavily]
[Geonyoung] Move!
-[breathing heavily]
-[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[sighs] Well, Mr. Jang.
You did a bang-up job here.
Now that you've seen it,
what do you think?
[chuckling]
I think
every single one of those pricks
is gonna wind up behind bars.
That old geezer.
He really held on, didn't he?
Eighteen damn years in this chair.
And just when I thought
it was finally my turn…
Goddamn it.
Looks like that bald asshole
Hwang is gonna take it.
So, Kitae.
Yes, sir.
What are you gonna do now?
Huh?
Hey.
You just gonna go down like this?
There's something
I'd like your approval for.
It's very important.
Hwang Daesik.
I wanna take care of him.
I'll do it myself.
You really think you can handle that?
Oh, it would be my pleasure.
I'll do it my own way.
[♪ intriguing music playing]